[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]
yeah he's a feeler though I'm a
是的，虽然我是一个
confluent and we're gonna be talking
汇合，我们将要谈论
about spring obviously right Oh who here
大概是 Spring 吧
for a foursome Kafka Kafka streams who
对于一个四人卡夫卡卡夫卡流谁
here has heard of spring who here has
这里听说过 Spring
heard of Kafka
听说卡夫卡
okay well this is not that it's all
好吧，这不是全部
about JMS so it's gonna be great okay
关于JMS，那就太好了
lights it's light lots of slides um
点亮很多幻灯片
actually it's here so basically this is
实际上它在这里，基本上这是
the only slide this is the most
唯一的幻灯片是最
important slide that you need to take a
您需要拍摄的重要幻灯片
picture of take a picture and the go
拍照留念
grab this thing called github and
抓住这个叫做github的东西，
everything is there works or not if
一切是否存在，如果
you're interested in code so we're gonna
您对代码感兴趣，所以我们要
have to go as quickly as possible
必须尽快走
through everything that we're gonna talk
通过我们要谈论的一切
about today and sort of hope to finish
今天左右，希望结束
it in time and we've got a lot to cover
及时处理，我们有很多要讲的
yes we're gonna go from absolute basics
是的，我们将脱离绝对基础
to all the way to the Kafka streams and
一直到卡夫卡溪流
spring cloud streams and all the things
Spring 的云流和所有的东西
so like my buddy David Coverdale used to
就像我的好友David Coverdale曾经
say prepare your brain melts so we start
说准备你的大脑融化，所以我们开始
with the something that's like a premise
就像前提一样
yeah can we bring the black screen Oh No
是的，我们可以带黑屏吗？
let's bring white screen this let's
让我们带白屏，让我们
bring your favorite place so we can
带上您最喜欢的地方，以便我们可以
build a new software the goal today is
构建新软件今天的目标是
just to kind of take a look at data
只是看一下数据
processing with Kafka I think Kafka it's
用卡夫卡处理我认为卡夫卡是
it's dangerous to think of Kafka is just
想到卡夫卡只是危险的
being another message queue right it I
是另一个消息队列吧
don't think a lot of people I think the
不要以为很多人我认为
people that are using coffee cups
使用咖啡杯的人
successfully aren't using it
成功地没有使用它
because they can use it as a traditional
因为他们可以将其作为传统
like replacement for Janice or something
例如替换珍妮丝之类的东西
like that it's it's more that because it
那样的原因更多是因为
scales so well it's become like a vein
如此好地缩放，变得像一条静脉
for data in the organization right it's
对于组织中的数据，
become a way to move it's not just about
成为一种移动的方式，而不仅仅是
event it's about the movement of data
事件是关于数据的移动
across the organization and when you
整个组织中以及当您
start to think of it like that as as
开始像那样思考它
another part of your data layer it
数据层的另一部分
becomes another kind of database then
变成另一种数据库
interesting things become possible it's
有趣的事情成为可能
not just about moving those small events
不只是要移动那些小事件
that then trigger action on some
然后触发一些动作
database it is the database right and so
数据库是数据库的权利等等
we're gonna talk about that today we're
我们今天要谈论的是
gonna start with treating it as a
首先将其视为
message queue kinda yeah kinda and after
消息队列还不错，之后
that we'll switch to more like a
我们将切换为更像
processing layer where we can do
我们可以做的处理层
event-driven micro service type of thing
事件驱动的微服务类型的事物
where you have a logic of processing
您有处理逻辑的地方
data built in in your application
应用程序中内置的数据
and the storage is separated at in
并且存储在
stores inside the kafka right so okay
卡夫卡里面的商店就好了
simplification we're gonna go to my
简化我们要去我的
second favorite place in the Internet of
互联网第二受欢迎的地方
course after production start dot spring
生产开始后的过程点Spring
that I are gonna build an application
我将要建立一个应用程序
here called Kafka and we're gonna use a
这里叫做Kafka，我们将使用
lot of different stuff may use Kafka
许多不同的东西可能会使用卡夫卡
itself
本身
Lombok we're gonna use Kafka strings and
lombok ，我们将使用卡夫卡琴弦和
we're gonna use spring cloud stream so
我们将使用 Spring 的云流，所以
what we're actually using is spring
我们实际使用的是 Spring
cloud stream Kafka streams which is a
云流卡夫卡流是
bit of a mouthful but it works anything
一点点的嘴，但它能起作用
else nope that should be fine that
否则不应该很好
should be fine a web maybe but we really
应该是可以上网的，但是我们真的
don't know we're using too like a stable
不知道我们使用的像马stable一样
like you said like we want to be in
就像你说的那样，我们想进入
production we do stable stuff and
生产我们做稳定的东西
production generate okay all right and
生产产生好的，好吧，
so the goal here is to build an
所以这里的目标是建立一个
application that actually yeah what kind
实际上是什么样的应用程序
of domain domain so here's the thing
的域域，这就是事情
like a weird thing to to say but I kind
有点奇怪的话要说，但是我很友善
of love watch movies and like these days
喜欢看电影，并且喜欢这些天
is all about the ratings of boomers
关于婴儿潮一代的收视率
people go check the Metacritic people go
人们去检查Metacritic人们去
check the Rotten Tomatoes people gonna
检查烂番茄的人会
check like a Facebook for some opinions
像Facebook一样查看一些意见
for some reason I don't know yes who's
由于某种原因，我不知道是谁
seen it so we need to scrap some of the
看到了，所以我们需要报废一些
spoilers that you prepared so yeah sorry
你准备的剧透所以很抱歉
about that next time
关于下一次
oh I'm waiting for episode the next
哦，我等下一集
episode then I can start watching it now
然后我就可以开始观看了
finally understand all those references
最终了解所有这些参考
anyway yeah so this is like about like a
是的，所以这就像一个
movies not about TV show so it's about
电影不是关于电视节目的，而是关于
writing a streaming application that
编写一个流应用程序
will generate ratings or like we get
会产生评分或类似我们得到的
their movies rated
他们的电影评分
and for that matter we're gonna be using
为此，我们将使用
Kafka right naturally and in order to
卡夫卡自然而然地
use Kafka the data that we're gonna use
使用Kafka我们将使用的数据
the data that we're gonna move around in
我们将要移动的数据
our system it's actually it's very
我们的系统实际上是非常
enterprise format is it's it's a pipe
企业格式是管道
delimited text very enterprise form how
分隔文本非常企业形式如何
many you guys in ladies from FinTech or
许多来自金融科技界的女士们
like banking industries I mean you're
像银行业，我是说你
dealing with the streaming data in pipe
处理管道中的流数据
delimited format
分隔格式
yes guys do not need to be shy and
是的，伙计们不必害羞，
ashamed about this one we're all doing
我们都在为这个感到愧
this it's okay it's okay yeah yeah so we
这没关系，没关系，是的，所以我们
essentially will take this data in the
本质上将在
in the in the file format and we
在文件格式中，我们
streaming to Kafka we start we will add
流媒体到卡夫卡，我们开始，我们将添加
the velocity to this data from 0 to
从0到此数据的速度
infinity so and to do that we're going
无限，要做到这一点，我们要
to be using some some data that George
使用一些乔治的数据
will just bring this on right so we need
只会使这个正确，所以我们需要
it we need to actually bring the data in
我们需要实际将数据导入
in order to bring it in we're gonna use
为了将其引入我们将使用
a format called Avro right yeah
是一种称为Avro的格式，是的
oh ok so we need to like remember
哦，好的，我们需要喜欢记住
elementally like like lethal weapon so
就像致命武器一样
we'll use Avro and and no pressure man I
我们将使用Avro，而且没有压力，我
just yeah so because we use Avro I am
是的，所以因为我们使用Avro
going to bring in the support for Avro
将为Avro提供支持
here we're gonna go to our little
在这里，我们要去我们的小
project I'm gonna open up the palm down
我要打开手掌的项目
XML and we're gonna do some terrible
XML，我们要做一些可怕的事情
things to our dependencies you mean in
你对我们依赖的东西
copy pasting dependencies that's a
复制粘贴的依赖项是
terrible thing is how we program things
糟糕的是我们如何编程
there's not everything
没有一切
unfortunately there is no like start of
不幸的是，没有像这样的开始
spring that I offer for everything right
我为一切做好的 Spring
it should be for I don't know like for
应该是因为我不知道喜欢
lunch or for dinner so here is this
午餐或晚餐，这是这里
we're gonna bring in the confluent
我们要把汇合处
support for a schema registry by the way
顺便支持架构注册表
we've got um you can what we're gonna do
我们有你可以做到的
is when use a schema registry to store
是使用架构注册表进行存储的时间
information about the type of data that
有关数据类型的信息
we're gonna conduct across the wire
我们将跨线进行
we're gonna use coffee itself
我们要自己喝咖啡
kafka requires zookeeper you've got a
卡夫卡要求 Zookeeper 你有一个
whole you know just a whole zoo of crazy
整个你都知道整个疯狂的动物园
like processes running that have nothing
像正在运行的进程一样
to do with what we're doing and so
与我们正在做的事情有关
exactly this is the what the people like
正是这就是人们喜欢的
this video right great so rather than
这个视频很好，所以而不是
doing that yourself I found that there I
自己做，我发现那里我
guess calm flow and have this very handy
猜测平静的气流，并非常方便
little thing called the confluent see
小东西叫合流见
you'll I know but it's a oh do come flow
你会知道的，但这是一个哦
platform okay so the confluent encounter
平台还可以，所以汇合的相遇
what would you were contributing to
您将为什么做出贡献
apache Kafka project and we also one of
apache Kafka项目，我们也是
the companies who has their own
有自己的公司
implementation of not the implementation
执行不执行
but at least like a packaged version of
但至少像
Apache Kafka and one of the tools that
Apache Kafka和其中的工具之一
were aiming for developers who don't
针对那些没有
want to at least have their brains
至少要有他们的大脑
melted by you know known zookeeper craft
被你知道的 Zookeeper 工艺融化
the schema reduce all these things wired
该架构减少了所有这些连接
we have a confluence Eli that allows you
我们有一个融合的礼来让您
to start different components so what we
开始不同的组件，所以我们
will do we will use the confluence Eli
会做的，我们会使用汇合的Eli
and to start on zookeeper Kafka schema
并以Zookeeper Kafka模式开始
registry with one command right
具有一个命令权限的注册表
destroy yes you should start every time
销毁是的，你应该每次开始
with counseling destroy so this is very
咨询销毁，所以这是非常
useful because you might have some of
有用，因为您可能有一些
the leftovers from the sub because Kafka
子的剩余物，因为卡夫卡
remembers you know here's the reference
记得你知道这是参考
for for Game of Thrones fans Kafka
为《权力的游戏》粉丝Kafka
remembers and this why you need to like
记得，这就是为什么你需要喜欢
a white pop stuff so start over and
白色的流行音乐，所以从头开始，
that's why the jaws did brilliant job
这就是为什么下巴做得很出色
calling my favorite command now we're
现在调用我最喜欢的命令
gonna start again and schema registry
将再次开始和架构注册表
depends on zookeeper which sorry it
取决于对不起的 Zookeeper
depends on Kafka which depends and
取决于卡夫卡，这取决于和
zookeeper so this is gonna bring up
Zookeeper ，所以这将带来
everything required to start it and so
启动它所需的一切，等等
that's fine I don't have to specify the
很好，我不必指定
other other things in between ok so
之间的其他其他事情还可以
that's gonna start up and now once
那将会开始，现在一次
that's there I've got these plugins here
在那里，我在这里有这些插件
yeah and this plugins are gonna convert
是的，这个插件会转换
a schema definition an avro schema
模式定义avro模式
definition into objects that I can use
定义成我可以使用的对象
in order for that to be true I need to
为了做到这一点，我需要
have the actual schema files and I'm
有实际的架构文件，我
gonna get them from my source main
要从我的主要来源那里获取它们
resources reason for that is that we as
资源的原因是我们作为
developers were lazy so it's much much
开发人员很懒，所以很多
more better when you have someone or
当有人或
something to generate your job objects
生成您的工作对象的东西
so we use this format of Avro as a
因此我们将这种格式的Avro用作
contract and we'll use in maven plug-in
合同，我们将在Maven插件中使用
to generate our Java POJO it's kind of
来生成我们的Java POJO
sort of poggio but it also has a notion
有点像钢琴，但它也有一个概念
about how to serialize object how to do
关于如何序列化对象怎么办
survive object so it's a little bit more
幸存的物体，所以要多一点
smarter chain just yet just a POJO
更智能的链，只是一个POJO
so we're going to be using this kind of
所以我们将使用这种
thing for movies we will have like
电影的东西，我们会喜欢
important properties of the movie ID
电影ID的重要属性
title of normal year director actors
正常年度导演演员称号
genre and so far and so on so all these
种类，到目前为止等等
nice teachers we have in in this error
我们在这个错误中有很好的老师
format but I need the plug-in to do that
格式，但我需要使用插件来完成
I need maybe plugin that's this thing
我可能需要这个插件
right here alright so build plugins oh
就在这里，所以建立插件哦
okay look at that so there's the aramean
好吧，那是阿拉伯人
plugin in order for all of that to work
插件，以便所有这些都能正常工作
of course you need the right repository
当然，您需要正确的存储库
so make sure you add that as well
因此，请确保同时添加
okay so repositories okay good stuff and
好吧，所以仓库好东西，
then from there just do your one very
然后从那里做你的一个非常
small maven clean install away from
小Maven干净安装远离
satisfaction here we go go go go so
满意在这里，我们去吧，去吧，所以
during this build it will fall right in
在这个构建过程中，它会落在
this plugin will find this Avro files
这个插件会找到这个Avro文件
inside this repository in this LA
在这个洛杉矶的这个仓库里
a resources folder and generate all
资源文件夹并生成所有
these classes that we'll be using for
这些我们将用于的类
this for for-4 movies etc movie Java and
这对于for-4电影等电影Java和
ratings don't worry about it just look
收视率不用担心，只是看一下
away okay ignore that terrifying tight
离开好吧，不用担心那可怕的紧
now what are we to do I want to look
现在我们要做什么我想看看
we're gonna do two things we gotta get
我们要做两件事
some data in there yep and then we got
是的，有些数据，然后我们得到了
to get some data out yes but I don't
得到一些数据是的，但我没有
want it's we're not just doing data in
希望是我们不只是在做数据
data out well we want what we want to do
做好数据，我们想要我们想要做的
is actually write data to the to the cue
实际上是将数据写入提示
to the broker yes and then gather
给经纪人，然后收集
insights and derive insights I
洞察力并获得洞察力
understand what the data means and how
了解数据的含义以及方式
we can what you know what we can do to
我们可以知道您能做什么
process it and we are dealing with
处理它，我们正在处理
potentially large amounts of data so
潜在的大量数据
we're gonna create a loader first yes so
我们要先创建一个加载器
it seems depressed to make it to make it
使它显得沮丧
more streaming type of thing so what we
更多的流媒体类型的东西，所以我们
need to do in this case we need to have
在这种情况下我们需要做的是
this kind of the producer the guy who
这种制片人
will be generate some data so we're
将产生一些数据，所以我们
gonna be create the class that will call
将创建将调用的类
producer where we will inject whatever
生产者我们将注入什么
beautiful things to to to apps so I'm
美丽的东西到应用程序，所以我
gonna create a new package here called
要在这里创建一个新包
producer and another one called analyzer
制片人和另一个叫做分析器的人
and into there and you yep alright so
进入那里，你是的，所以
with the with the producer so what we
与生产者在一起，所以我们
doing here is producer right so we have
在这里做是对生产者的权利，所以我们有
a class we have a Lombok so we can have
一班我们有 lombok ，所以我们可以有
all these beautiful things that Lombok
lombok 所有这些美丽的东西
does what's constructor yeah required RX
请问RX需要什么构造函数
constructor logging is obviously we do
构造函数日志记录显然是我们要做的
in log4j version two right now you have
在log4j版本2中，现在您有了
a need to type it log yep yeah and
需要输入它是，是的，
obviously it's gonna be component right
显然它将是正确的
yeah so a what we need to do in in real
是的，这是我们真正需要做的
life there's two classes the producer
人生有两个班制片人
and consumer in this case we're going to
和消费者在这种情况下，我们将
be focusing on the producer side of
专注于生产者方面
things here but we're not going to be
事情在这里，但我们不会
using this because spring
用这个是因为 Spring
has even better thing that's called
有更好的东西叫做
Kafka simply how many of you guys in
卡夫卡只是你们中有多少人
ladies work with if the thing called
女士们一起工作，如果事情叫
something-something template head spring
东西模板头Spring
so in this case you know exactly what to
所以在这种情况下，您确切知道该怎么做
expect so you need to have this whatever
期待，所以你需要拥有这个
we call it let's go we have a two topics
我们称之为走吧，我们有两个主题
to produce and we will call this the
生产，我们将其称为
movie producer and Rainey's producer so
电影制片人和雷尼的制片人
in this case we will have Kafka
在这种情况下，我们将拥有卡夫卡
templates first one will go with long is
模板第一个将使用很长的时间是
our type and goes with movie is our
我们的类型和电影一起去是我们的
value we will call it obviously movie
值，我们将其称为电影
Kafka template key for every message and
每封邮件的Kafka模板密钥和
then you have the value of the message
那么你就拥有了信息的价值
so again it's not like a message queue
再次，这不像消息队列
it's not just a job you tilt queue that
倾斜队列不仅是一项工作，
stores data there's actually it's more
存储数据，实际上更多
like a map right you can actually index
就像地图一样，您实际上可以将其编入索引
into the messages in the queue by their
通过他们进入队列中的消息
key and so when you work with a Kafka
键，所以当您使用Kafka时
template you have to think about both
模板，您必须同时考虑两者
the type of the key and the time value
键的类型和时间值
in in order to make this work we need to
为了使这项工作，我们需要
have some sort of the configuration so
有某种配置，所以
well so yeah
好吧，是的
in this case we need to have a
在这种情况下，我们需要
configuration class so can we can we use
配置类，这样我们就可以使用
a configuration here yes we also win
这里的配置是的，我们也赢了
this case configuration we just put this
这种情况下，我们只是把这个
here so let's put the pins here yeah so
在这里，让我们将别针放在这里
we we will try to deploy this in
我们将尝试将其部署在
production now so for in order to work
现在生产以便工作
this work we need to have this okay so
这项工作，我们需要有这个好吧
yeah in order to work this we need to
是的，为了做到这一点，我们需要
have we need to pass the configuration
我们需要通过配置吗
yeah yep so we will have the how it's
是的，所以我们会知道
called producer factory yes
叫生产者工厂
producer default default or is it
生产者默认默认值还是
default producer
默认生产者
factory yeah before producer factory
是的，在生产工厂之前
factory so what it does we need to
工厂，所以我们需要做什么
return all this
全部归还
something new default default producer
一些新的默认默认生产者
factory so in this case this guy also
工厂，在这种情况下，这个家伙也
know a lot of things about spring craft
对Spring 工艺了解很多
a framework knows a lot of things about
一个框架知道很多事情
how to configure so there is lots of
如何配置，所以有很多
things if you do in this local
如果你在这个地方做的话
development you don't need to provide
您不需要提供的开发
like a local whole step of things but
就像当地的整个步骤
like in this case we need to provide all
像在这种情况下，我们需要提供所有
this information because we're going to
这些信息，因为我们要
be using a verse Kim registry we need to
使用金诗句注册表，我们需要
provide information services these are
提供信息服务的是
wiser the things that the George just
明智的乔治只是
mentioned that a key in value will be
提到价值的关键是
sterilized during the time where are we
我们在哪里消毒过
doing this where we will replace it
这样做，我们将取代它
through so the we have this map
通过，所以我们有这张地图
something something called config map
所谓的配置图
config new hash map and would be shrink
配置新的哈希图，将被缩小
and we string and in this case we will
然后我们串起，在这种情况下，我们将
do observe like start programming : and
确实像开始编程那样观察：和
I was forgetting this you can see
我忘记了这个，你可以看到
exactly so we will have this gun thing
正是这样，我们将拥有这把枪的东西
and think will work it's a live coding
并认为这将是现场编码
so we will have this bootstrap URL
所以我们会有这个引导网址
producer config so we have this producer
生产者配置，所以我们有这个生产者
config and we have a bootstrap URL in
配置，我们在其中有一个引导网址
this case we will say it's gonna be
在这种情况下，我们会说它将
localhost 1992 we'll have here can think
localhost 1992我们将在这里考虑
thing for what the source we need to
需要什么来源的东西
have a schema register euro so in this
有一个模式注册欧元
case we're going to be schema registry
情况下，我们将成为架构注册表
ray g3 you are Al and we need to have a
ray g3您是Al，我们需要有一个
HTTP obviously in production to do HTTP
HTTP显然在生产中要做HTTP
localhost
localhost
1981 and two more things are responsible
1981年，另外两件事负责
for reducer config producer config and
用于减速器配置生产者配置和
we need to have a key sterilizer kiss
我们需要一个关键的消毒吻
your Eliza class in this case it's gonna
在这种情况下，您的Eliza班级将会
be the
成为
the long naturally so in this case
在这种情况下自然很长
there's a plenty of those but we need to
有很多，但我们需要
want for Kafka class and another thing
想要卡夫卡课和另一件事
since we're going to be using all this
因为我们将要使用所有这些
awesome stuff for ever oh it will work
永远很棒的东西哦，它将起作用
so we have this the producer config and
所以我们有生产者配置和
value sterilizer so 2 2 2 and we will
值消毒器，所以2 2 2我们将
have Kafka a bro a bro AF have ro
有卡夫卡一个兄弟一个兄弟有AF
serializer there's plenty of stuff what
序列化器有很多东西
we need to use only one this one class
我们只需要在这一堂课中使用一个
alright so and so we have this conflict
好吧，所以我们有这个冲突
right so we're passing this to default
对的，所以我们将其传递给默认值
factory now we have two things the
工厂现在我们有两件事
config so that potentially should be it
配置，所以可能应该是它
in in our configuration the next thing
在我们的配置中，下一件事
that we need to do in we need to have a
我们需要做的是
topic definition because Kafka is
主题定义，因为Kafka是
dealing with this concept of topics and
处理主题概念和
topic is the entity that we distribute
主题是我们分配的实体
across multiple Kafka knows so cool
跨多个卡夫卡知道很酷
thing is that the spring craft
事情是，Spring 工艺
integration thing the spring Kafka
整合物 Spring 卡夫卡
project has ability to create topics for
项目具有创建主题的能力
us
我们
so the I think I missed bin okay
所以我想我想念斌了
the there is a class new topic so
有一个新的课程主题
topic topic and would you return new
topic topic，您会返回新的
topic okay new new again this it's it's
主题好吧，新的，新的，再次，这是
also I blame Kotlin because I start just
我也怪Kotlin，因为我刚开始
set my things so the topic name we have
设置我的东西，以便我们拥有主题名称
this topic with the movies and it's a
电影中的这个话题，这是一个
it's a configuration that will be
这是一个配置
responsible for durability of your data
负责数据的持久性
replication factor and we're going to be
复制因子，我们将成为
doing very cool stuff here
在这里做很酷的事情
meaning that's you know yellow there's
意思是你知道黄色
no replication yep and we'll do rating
没有复制是，我们会做评级
smooth ratings topic right and would you
顺利进行评分主题，对吗？
return new new topic and the same thing
返回新的新主题和同一件事
would you for for ratings and so one of
请问您的收视率，所以其中之一
the things that usually developers do is
开发人员通常要做的是
pre provision these topics before or
在或之前预先设置这些主题
some operations people provision so the
一些操作人员提供，所以
cool thing about this this integration
这个集成的很棒的事情
or this this code that you don't need to
或此代码，您不需要
do a checks that if topic is existed it
检查是否存在主题
will just use it and I will just use
会用它而我会用
this definition and inject here if topic
此定义并在此处插入主题
doesn't exist it will create this so and
不存在，它将如此创建并
it's cool thing that spring provides
Spring 提供的很酷的东西
this these capabilities yeah exactly
这些功能正是
so will it work because in this case we
它将起作用，因为在这种情况下，我们
have wonderful Factory and the spring
有美好的工厂和 Spring
will be able to figure this out by type
将能够按类型弄清楚
yes so I will be typing George will be
是的，所以我要输入George
factoring plus so since we have this
加上因素，因为我们有这个
data in the format that is very
数据格式非常
enterprising meaning this text format we
进取的意思是我们这种文本格式
need to do parsing so we will bring a
需要进行解析，因此我们将带来一个
small thing called parser after we will
我们将在之后称为解析器的小东西
refactor the application
重构应用
it's called severe case of OCD okay no
被称为强迫症的严重病例
no si Jin barf scroll down scroll down
没有si Jin barf向下滚动向下滚动
up up up up up you see this is graphical
起来起来起来，你看到这是图形的
version so we we on the right track so
版本，所以我们在正确的轨道上
yeah so will you you go to you go to
是的，所以你会去你去
this guy so do Kafka topics and there's
这个家伙也是卡夫卡主题，
a comment called list and in this case
一个称为列表的注释，在这种情况下
we will have a zookeeper where is it it
我们将有一个 Zookeeper ，它在哪里
has a yes zookeeper so we do zookeeper
有一个 Zookeeper ，所以我们做 Zookeeper
and would you localhost 21 did you want
你会想要 localhost 21
so magic I think it's already halfway we
太神奇了，我想我们已经走了一半
created topics without creating topics
创建主题而不创建主题
using just a spring boot I think it's a
只用一个 spring boot ，我认为这是一个
it's a good stuff now poor sir ringing
这是个好东西，可怜的先生响了
the poor sir
可怜的先生
spring G about this bar so you just you
关于这个酒吧的 Spring G所以你就是你
read the line and you do you know
阅读该行，你知道吗
neither neither Victor I are proud of
我也不以维克多为荣
this code at no point when we wrote this
我们编写此代码时
did we say to each other
我们是否互相说过
good job whoa well it uses streams you
干得好，它使用流您
see it's some water and cold it's early
看到天气有些冷
there's something to be proud of right
有一些值得骄傲的事情
alright so bring the file in so we need
好了，所以把文件放进去，所以我们需要
to read the file from somewhere so in
从某处读取文件
this case we need to have our and both
在这种情况下，我们需要同时
endpoint for our application
我们应用程序的端点
I'm gonna reveal that the finder I'm
我要告诉我我是发现者
gonna copy copy pasta this over here
要在这里复制意大利面
okay sure
好吧，当然
don't break whoa so that's that's not no
不要打破哇，那不是
it's quite a bit because it has 900
相当多，因为它有900
lines of text it's quite quite not so
文字行相当不是
not so much bigger yep some sprinkle
不是那么大是一些洒
movie so in this case we're gonna be
电影，在这种情况下，我们将成为
using this file but in real life
在现实生活中使用此文件
the way how it works with the kafka
kafka的工作方式
pipelines it either after connect will
连接后的管道将
be listen to this data from some legacy
聆听一些旧数据
data source like database and pumping
数据源，例如数据库和抽水
this data into Kafka or it can be used
将此数据导入Kafka或可以使用
the same producer-consumer to to do the
同一生产者-消费者去做
thing so in this case we will do
所以在这种情况下，我们会做
old-school way we will read the file or
老式的方式，我们将读取文件或
read the line by line alright so I don't
一行一行地阅读，所以我不
remember like how to read the file from
记得喜欢如何从中读取文件
this from all right where is it where is
好的，这在哪里
it just let's let's copy let's copy our
它只是让我们复制让我们复制我们的
method and save good stuff so since we
方法并保存好东西，所以既然我们
like I said we were not proud of doing
就像我说过的那样，我们并不为此感到自豪
these things
这些东西
yep and this is what we do right so
是的，这就是我们的正确做法
we're gonna do this we're gonna do this
我们要这样做我们要这样做
we're gonna be copying pasting things so
我们将要复制粘贴内容，以便
to do so so this is this is good stuff
这样做，所以这是好东西
right so do you import or port on demand
对，所以您可以按需进口或港口
and now we're reading this movie file
现在我们正在看电影文件
and do we have a right version of Java
我们有正确的Java版本吗
probably yeah yeah so move it in play do
可能是的，所以在游戏中移动它
we have it working quality let's call it
我们有它的工作质量，我们称之为
slices we have here right move it in
切片，我们在这里右移
place all right so next one where's our
放好，所以下一个是我们的
template where's it doesn't work move it
模板在哪里不起作用移动它
okay so movie topic is some of the
好吧，电影主题是一些
constants that we also will copy because
我们也将复制的常量，因为
this is this is cool stuff the two two
这是两个很酷的东西
names of the topics usually we're using
我们通常使用的主题名称
the spring boot configuration on things
spring boot 配置的东西
like that to pass this kind of
像这样通过这种
configuration and if you're running this
配置，如果您正在运行此
in in some sort of I released a new
在某种程度上，我发布了新的
spring tips video every Wednesday
每个星期三的 Spring 提示视频
there's a new video and yesterday I
有一个新视频，昨天我
introduced how to use spring batch to
介绍了如何使用spring batch来
process large amounts of data from Kafka
处理来自Kafka的大量数据
for ETL exactly like what we're doing
与我们正在做的ETL完全一样
here I really think I should have
在这里我真的认为我应该有
brought that up before we got in stage
在我们上台之前提出来
though it might have been a different
虽然可能有所不同
talk spring branching out the spring
说话的 Spring 分支 Spring
stream Oh coma is you injecting this one
流哦，昏迷你要注射这个吗
is over here why it is not we're
在这里，为什么不是我们
oh it's not assigned to anything that's
哦，它没有分配给任何
fair yes
不错
great point good stuff he's been writing
他一直在写的好东西
a lot of Kotlin and so in Kotlin the
很多Kotlin，所以在Kotlin
constructor is the storage yeah don't
构造函数是存储是的，不要
yeah just yeah and then you're gonna see
是的，只是，然后你会看到
when I do my next talk I'm gonna be
当我做下一个演讲时，我会
doing it with rate sang and he's he's
用率唱来做，他是
gonna be struggling if your your your
如果你是你的你会挣扎
quad okay okay good all right okay good
四人好的好的好的好的好的
okay template template we have a
好的模板模板，我们有一个
different name right yeah and so as you
是不同的名字，是的，所以和你一样
can see this this the how we call it all
可以看到这就是我们如何称呼它
this like a framework programming is
这就像框架编程是
basically just a jar going around with
基本上只是一个罐子
some copy pasting things this is what
一些复制粘贴的东西，这是什么
you find in the internet that just you
你在互联网上发现只有你
copy paste but exactly so two things so
复制粘贴，但是恰好有两件事
we do have our template for movies we
我们确实有电影模板
will use this to produce this data this
将使用它来产生这个数据
this matter has different variation if
如果这件事有不同的变化
you like more like a synchronous style
你更喜欢同步风格
of programming there's like a playable
编程就像一个可玩的游戏
future or like a listen about future
未来或喜欢听未来
that can be turned into completable
可以变成可完成的
future now let's do it
现在就开始吧
we have a confluence you know I remember
我们有合流，你知道我记得
it's there just around the build just
它就在构建周围
remove this guy this remove yeah
删除这个家伙，这个删除是的
movies movies and yeah movies it's fine
电影电影和是的电影都很好
yeah perfect stream with speed of love
是的，完美的爱情流
remove these two dashes yep yep yeah
删除这两个破折号是是是
that will work
那可行
all right all right
好吧好吧
so accountancy like let's see if we
这样的会计，让我们看看是否
actually have something here so would
实际上这里有东西，所以
you
您
where's our terminal terminal would you
请问我们的终点站在哪里
a confluent
合流
writings oops writings right and we
作品哎呀作品正确，我们
should see some stuff data is streamed
应该看到一些数据流
but one second people were saying what
但是有一秒钟的人在说什么
the hell what is that I will tell you
到底我要告诉你什么
because we didn't specify value format
因为我们没有指定值格式
now behold ah just that one chicken you
现在看到啊，那只鸡你
see everything differently okay yes so
看到一切都不同好吧，是的
yes so there isn't a reason for that
是的，所以没有理由
okay yep terminal ah we need to do it
是的，是的，终端啊，我们需要这样做
because it's a full screen swipe swipe
因为这是全屏滑动
swipe yeah so reason for that so we
刷是的，所以这样做的原因是这样，我们
start reading the data from or
开始从或读取数据
generating the data in in our java file
在我们的java文件中生成数据
and after that we send this data to
然后我们将这些数据发送到
Kafka here's the thing Kafka really
Kafka这就是Kafka真正的东西
don't care what kind of stuff you will
不在乎你会什么样的东西
put in there some people even put files
放一些人甚至放文件
there I'm not saying this is a good idea
我不是说这是个好主意
probably if you start putting these
也许如果你开始把这些
files in Kafka you need to consider your
卡夫卡中的文件，您需要考虑您的
life choices in general so but I'm not
人生一般的选择，但我不是
the one to judge so the thing is we
一个可以判断的就是我们
actually try to with the binary format
实际上尝试使用二进制格式
we're trying to simplify and reduce
我们正在尝试简化和减少
payload so this why you would see this
有效负载，这就是为什么您会看到此内容
output of this binary data because
此二进制数据的输出，因为
console would not be able to read this
控制台将无法读取此内容
out and things like the average binary
出来，像平均二进制
format another thing we store schema in
格式化我们存储架构的另一件事
in not to to as a part of our payload so
不作为我们有效载荷的一部分
in this case our payload becomes even
在这种情况下，我们的有效负载变为偶数
smaller and we don't store the scheme of
较小，我们不存储方案
every message so next time when you try
每条消息，以便下次您尝试时
to read this scheme readership will
阅读此计划的读者将
return this and it will be also locally
返回这个，它也会在本地
cached inside your application return
缓存在您的应用程序返回中
the schema and the serializer because
模式和序列化程序，因为
our the binary palat knows how to
我们的二元菜知道如何
deserialize itself will just be you know
反序列化本身就是您知道的
invoked and we'll bring stuff in alright
被调用，我们会把东西带进来
so we have a data in now we need to
所以我们现在有一个数据，我们需要
start doing some process 20 we have
开始做一些过程20
plenty spring code stream is a
Spring 的代码流是一个
technology that allows you to
使您能够
to describe messaging brokers in a
描述消息代理中的
generic sort of fashion you can
可以的通用时尚
extricate the the wiring that the
拔掉
routing of these brokers into the config
将这些代理路由到配置中
files and then spring code stream
文件，然后Spring 代码流
materializes the thing that you need to
实现您需要的东西
actually talk to that broker in an
确实在
efficient way so one way is to use the
有效的方法，因此一种方法是使用
Spring Framework messaging channel
Spring Framework消息传递通道
message channel rather abstraction and
消息通道相当抽象，
this allows you to think about
这可以让您考虑
downstream brokers as just being you
下游经纪人就像你一样
know things at the other end of a pipe
知道管道另一端的东西
the same kind of pipe that you would see
你会看到的那种管道
in in spring integration right now when
在 Spring Integration 中
I say pipe I I do mean to suggest I do
我说管道II确实意味着建议我这样做
mean to invoke the idea of a parka
意图引用皮大衣的想法
texture on the other hand if using
另一方面，如果使用纹理
spring cloud stream with kafka streams
卡夫卡溪流的spring-cloud-stream
you you can use types that are more
您可以使用更多类型
natural for people working with Kafka
与Kafka合作的人很自然
streams and in particular in Kafka
溪流，尤其是在卡夫卡
streams you have two ways of thinking
流你有两种思维方式
about data you've got what seems bring
关于您似乎拥有的数据
stop you right there because some people
阻止你就在那里，因为有人
might I don't know about Kafka Street
我可能不知道卡夫卡街
how many of you heard about Kafka
你们当中有多少人听说过卡夫卡
streams oh okay good you so Kafka
流哦，好吧，你好，卡夫卡
streets Kafka streams it's the it's just
卡夫卡街上流的只是
a library it's a part of Apache Kafka
一个库，它是Apache Kafka的一部分
it's embedded framework for stream
它是流的嵌入式框架
processing that's it's nothing more so
就是这样处理
this why it's a it's a well in the
这就是为什么这是一个很好的
notion of dealing with Kafka Oliver
与卡夫卡·奥利弗打交道的想法
Spring boot just just another job it's a
Spring Boot只是另一项工作
stream processing pipeline but when
流处理管道，但何时
you're working with Kafka streams you
您正在使用Kafka串流
get to you can build processing
可以建立处理
pipelines and for me the reason I became
管道，对我来说，我成为
interested in Kafka streams was I wanted
我想对卡夫卡流感兴趣
to do a lot of the things that people
做很多人做的事情
might otherwise do with something like
否则可能会像
spark I wanted to have that kind of
火花，我想拥有那种
functionality without having to deploy
功能而无需部署
and manage spark so I was looking for
和管理火花，所以我一直在寻找
something that you know I want I want as
你知道我想要的东西
much functionality as possible without
没有尽可能多的功能
having to pay that complexity cost goes
必须支付复杂性成本
to suffer in figuring out where your app
弄清楚您的应用程序在哪里
is running how to store your state like
正在运行如何像这样存储您的状态
how you would submit this job how you
您将如何提交这份工作
would do with some complex pipeline and
可以处理一些复杂的管道，
how to recover and all this stuff right
如何恢复以及所有这些东西正确
now Kafka it's long you've got Kafka in
现在卡夫卡很久了，你已经在卡夫卡了
your organization you can use Kafka
您的组织可以使用Kafka
streams Kafka is all you need in order
流卡夫卡是您订购所需的一切
to run this and so you can just write
运行它，所以你可以写
the code in in any language that spring
那个 Spring 用任何语言编写的代码
boots you know I can use spring boot
靴子，你知道我可以用 spring boot
plus Kafka streams very easily
加卡夫卡流很容易
and that's it so anything that supports
就是这样，任何支持的事情
spring boot Cartland java groovy
Spring Boot Cartland Java groovy
whatever Scala anything won't work just
无论Scala什么都行不通
fine in the world of Kafka screams
在Kafka的尖叫声中表现不错
you've got two types one is called a K
您有两种类型，一种叫做K
table what's a K table K table is the
桌子是什么K桌子K桌子是
representation of state so there's a two
国家的代表，所以有两个
type of things that you might have here
您可能在这里拥有的东西类型
history of the things and the state of
事物的历史和状态
the things so the state of the things
事物的状态
meaning that we can create this table
表示我们可以创建此表
and can say we know that for example
可以说我们知道例如
movie four particular more energy with
电影四个特别的能量
this moment of time has this particular
这个时候有这个特别
value the second one is obviously Kafka
值第二个显然是卡夫卡
streams which represents the history it
流代表了它的历史
represents the all facts that happened
代表发生的所有事实
within particular like time or whatnot
在特定的时间之类的时间内
so essentially what it does it maps into
所以本质上它映射到什么
Kafka streams maps into Kafka topic in
Kafka将地图流式传输到Kafka主题中
the caf K table maps into compact atop
caf K表映射到紧凑的顶部
so compact the topic a special type of
因此，将主题压缩为一种特殊的
storage inside the Kafka that stores
卡夫卡内部存储的存储
only latest and greatest value for
只有最新和最大的价值
particular key right
特定键权
and another thing just I just want to
还有另一件事我只是想
mention this because you mentioned
提到这个，因为你提到
different languages and I want to
不同的语言，我想
mention a little bit of assembly
提一点组装
language here so things like a consumer
这里的语言，所以像消费者
producer and a little bit of the Kafka
制片人和卡夫卡的一点点
template is what we consider as kind of
模板就是我们认为的
low-level API is you dealing with these
低级API是您处理这些
like sending messages individual
就像个人发送消息一样
messages where Kafka streams is more
卡夫卡流更多的消息
like allows you to deal with the
喜欢让您处理
functional approach Kafka stream has a
功能方法Kafka流具有
two two types two fields it's a DSL
两个两个类型两个字段，这是一个DSL
which looks like a Java 8 the stream API
看起来像Java 8流API
there's also proper processor API we're
还有适当的处理器API
not going to be touch this in this talk
在这次演讲中不会碰到这个
but it also allows you to build very
但它也可以让您建立
complex data pipelines so when you work
复杂的数据管道，因此在您工作时
with Kafka streams I know and with most
我所知道的，以及大多数
matches message messaging technologies
匹配消息传递技术
you have to think about there's a lot of
你必须考虑很多
things you need to care about first of
首先需要注意的事情
all how to what does this thing connect
所有如何连接到这个东西
and also since I'm writing generic Java
而且由于我正在编写通用Java
code I'm using a binding ok so this is
我正在使用绑定代码，所以这是
an interface here this interface defines
此接口定义的接口
the bindings that I want spring code
我想要 Spring 代码的绑定
stream to manage for me in my spring
在 Spring 为我管理
code stream Kafka strands application so
代码流Kafka串应用程序所以
I'm saying hey spring code stream I've
我说的是嘿，我的Spring代码流
got this thing this topic called movies
这个东西叫做电影
and now this is a logical name I'm just
现在这是一个逻辑名称
giving it in
给它
logical name that I can I can understand
我可以理解的逻辑名称
in my code that mapping from logical
在我的代码中，逻辑映射
name to the actual broker is done in
实际经纪人的姓名在
terms of configuration and so you can
配置条款，因此您可以
see here I've got movies as the logical
看到这里我把电影当成逻辑
name and in the configuration here I've
名称和配置在这里
got movies so it's a spring cut stream
有电影，所以这是春暖花开的溪流
bindings dot movies and then I specify
绑定点电影，然后我指定
things like the application ID I can
我可以的应用程序ID之类的东西
specify things like the destination in
指定诸如目的地之类的东西
the broker of the actual topic how we
实际话题的经纪人我们如何
should encode headings start headers how
应该对标题开始头进行编码
we should do decoding and all these
我们应该解码，所有这些
kinds of things get specified in
特定的东西在
configuration I don't have to worry
配置我不必担心
about all this because it's done in the
关于这一切，因为它是在
property file and that can live in the
属性文件，并且可以存在于
config server for example and spring
配置服务器的例子和 Spring
Club config server or somewhere else it
俱乐部配置服务器或其他地方
doesn't have to be in my java code where
不必在我的Java代码中
it's much harder to understand at a
很难理解
grant at a glance and it's also much
一目了然，这也很多
harder to change and obviously in
很难改变，显然在
production you might have different URLs
生产中您可能具有不同的URL
for scheme registry for Kafka bootstrap
用于Kafka引导程序的方案注册表
server so this information can be
服务器，以便此信息可以是
externalized
外在化
and even ejected during runtime yes so
甚至在运行时弹出
we've done we've extracted that out now
我们已经完成了提取
I'm just saying basically hey I'm
我只是说基本上我是
expecting to get data and I want to work
期望得到数据，我想工作
with it in terms of the K table API from
从K表API开始
the movies topic okay I've got data in
电影主题好吧，我有数据
the ratings topic and I expect to work
收视率主题，我希望能正常工作
with it as a case stream I've got data
作为案例流，我有数据
that's gonna be coming in from the
那将来自
average table topic and I expect some
平均表主题，我希望一些
work out there like this and so and then
像这样在那工作，然后
finally I have two outputs I expect to
最后我有两个输出
send data to these case streams okay so
将数据发送到这些案例流，这样
these are I can get a hold of these
这些是我可以掌握的这些
references they're fully initialized for
他们完全初始化的引用
me
我
by spring code stream and I can just
通过 Spring 代码流，我可以
start working on the data that's coming
开始处理即将到来的数据
off of them or I can start sending data
他们或者我可以开始发送数据
to them okay now in the case of the
对他们来说现在好了
output you don't actually use you don't
输出您实际上不使用您不
actually grab a hold of a reference to a
实际上抓住了对
case stream and send anything to that
案例流并将任何内容发送给
you in this case it would be not a
在这种情况下，您将不是
spring boat way or spring cloud way so
春船方式或Spring Cloud方式
we're going to be using dependency
我们将使用依赖
injection here right so now we're gonna
注射在这里，所以现在我们要
do two things I think the first thing is
做两件事我认为第一件事是
when a tell spring code stream to make
当告诉spring代码流时
its so and do that by saying at enable
它是这样，并在启用时说
bindings so here we go doc class and
绑定，所以在这里我们去doc类，
then we're gonna create a I think the
然后我们将创建一个
first thing I want to do is process the
我要做的第一件事是处理
game do we wanna enable enable Kafka
游戏我们要启用启用卡夫卡吗
streams as well okay should be done yeah
溪流也应该做
Yola yep so we're gonna be using like a
是的，我们要像
very sophisticated algorithm to figure
非常复杂的算法来计算
out the movie ratings so there's a
电影分级，所以有一个
different different ways how to do is
不同的不同方法是
using the more sophisticated one so
使用更复杂的一个
we're getting account of the ratings and
我们正在考虑收视率和
after that we do some of this railing
之后，我们要做一些这样的栏杆
and after that we divide some by by by
然后我们除以
count right so I'm going to create a
计数正确，所以我要创建一个
stream listener this is a spring boot
流侦听器，这是一个 spring boot
component regular springing boot
组件常规弹跳靴
component that's going to listen for
将要侦听的组件
messages coming in on the ratings topic
评分主题中出现的消息
is that true yes okay so bindings in
是真的吗，所以绑定
this case we really care about the
这种情况下我们真的很在乎
stream of ratings because our another
评级之流，因为我们的另一个
application another micro-services if
如果应用其他微服务
you another marker service if you like
如果您愿意，可以给您另一个标记服务
will be pumping data in so we interested
将要抽入数据，所以我们感兴趣
in all events that happens the story
在发生故事的所有事件中
with movies little different well we're
电影跟我们没什么两样
talking about movies when we will touch
谈论电影时，我们会碰触
base on this on this kind of thing okay
基于这样的事情还可以
and a source we have reading okay so
还有我们已经阅读的资料了
that's a long and reading incoming
那很长，阅读来信
readings so interesting thing here it's
在这里读书很有趣
that's that public void process okay the
那就是公共无效过程
interesting thing that the Kafka or
有趣的是，卡夫卡还是
sorry Spring Buddha sprinkle out streams
对不起，春佛洒出溪流
will be handling all these low-level
将处理所有这些低层次的
things including spring streams builder
包括Spring Streams Builder在内的东西
building topology starting Kafka streams
建立启动Kafka流的拓扑
application its everything will be
应用程序的一切都会
handled so in this case you only
这样处理，在这种情况下，您只
focusing on this thing called topology
专注于这个叫做拓扑的东西
so basically things with key stream and
所以基本上是带有密钥流的东西
key tables you building a topology of
您构建拓扑的关键表
your application how many of you folks
您的应用程序你们有多少人
have here a PhD in maybe graph theory
在这里获得图论博士学位
anyone okay so I can I can be smart for
任何人都可以，所以我可以很聪明
a couple seconds so here's the thing
几秒钟，这就是事情
there's a thing called directed acyclic
有一种叫做定向非循环的东西
graph and it's not not just a simple
图，而不仅仅是一个简单的图
graph it's the directed meaning that it
图是它的直接含义
has a beginning in the end and a cyclic
在结尾处有一个开头，在循环中
meaning that there's no loops in it so
意味着里面没有循环，所以
this is model that you used to to
这是您以前使用的模型
explain or describe any data pipeline so
解释或描述任何数据管道，以便
basically Kafka streams API provides you
基本上，Kafka Streams API为您提供
the way how you build your directed
您如何建立定向的方式
acyclic graph so it's cool that there's
非循环图，所以很酷
no like a PhD in graph theory here so I
不像这里的图论博士，所以我
can say
可以说
right that's fair perfect so the cool
对，这很完美，很酷
thing is that this application the Kafka
问题是该应用程序是Kafka
streams the pairwise the way how we can
双向传输成对流
describe your topology so you can grab
描述您的拓扑，以便您可以抓取
it and use the visualizer tool to see
并使用可视化工具查看
this graph so what I'm doing here is I'm
这个图，所以我在这里做的是
gonna say when the data comes in on the
要说的是当数据输入到
case stream I'm gonna reduce it I'm
案例流，我要减少它，我是
gonna turn it into a grouped stream no
要将其变成分组流
it does right okay it's gonna be a goop
没关系，好​​了
stream of ratings I'm gonna take all the
评分流，我要接受所有
ratings and then group them by the key
评分，然后按关键分组
right then finally from that I'm gonna
然后最后从那我要
get another cable out of the count then
然后再拿出另一根电缆
I'm gonna do a reduce here yep by adding
我要在这里减少添加
them together right yes as you can see
他们在一起，是的，如你所见
here we transform in one stream into the
在这里，我们将一个流转换为
group stream and after that we transform
组流，然后我们进行转换
group stream in the key table because we
在密钥表中分组流，因为我们
interested in this state and the way how
对这种状态和方式感兴趣
a collecting state the count and the end
收集状态的计数和结束
is in the end the sum is the way because
最终，总和就是这样，因为
the key table has this method so ratings
密钥表具有此方法，因此评分
stream that count returns the key table
计数的流返回密钥表
that will have all information about
将具有有关的所有信息
particular key and the running running
特定的键和运行中的运行
sum and one of the things that you
总和和你所要做的一件事
probably will notice and will not notice
可能会注意到，不会注意到
in this code there's no way how we can
在这段代码中，我们没有办法
specify storage like if we use in
指定存储空间，就像我们在
database or we using a file or we just
数据库，或者我们使用文件，或者我们只是
storing this in hash map so all these
将其存储在哈希图中，所以所有这些
things is handled by kafka streams kafka
事情由卡夫卡流卡夫卡处理
streams is delay is the framework that
流是延迟是框架
provides you ability to do stateful
提供您做有状态的能力
stream processing meaning that you when
流处理意味着您何时
you're calculating things like sum or if
您正在计算总和或
you count you in order to calculate the
您数数您以计算
current step you need to have a state
当前步骤，您需要有一个状态
from the past right so and kafka streams
从过去的权利和卡夫卡流
got you covered so it has a variety of
让你被覆盖，所以它有各种各样的
state stores it can be used persistent
状态存储，可以持久使用
state stored in this case it will be
在这种情况下存储的状态将是
small instance of the rocks DB that will
岩石数据库的小实例
have all this information can be in
有所有这些信息可以在
memory store there is API how we can
内存存储中有API我们该如何
plan out your own store and cool think
计划自己的商店，冷静思考
about this state store it's also
关于这个州立商店
replicated through Kafka so if the
通过Kafka复制，因此如果
application wall breaks it will have a
应用程序墙中断将有一个
change log topic inside the Kafka so
更改卡夫卡内部的日志主题
next time when you restart this
下次重新启动时
application you don't need to reprocess
您不需要重新处理的应用程序
everything you can retrieve the state
您可以检索状态的一切
from the Kafka so working yep let's
来自卡夫卡，所以工作是，让我们
what should we see um so what did you do
我们应该看到什么，所以你做了什么
map the values did it can't move trying
映射无法移动的值
to prepare K Street Oh see oh we've got
准备K街哦，哦，我们有
some things that aren't being used yet
一些尚未使用的东西
so we want readings we don't want movies
所以我们想要阅读我们不想要电影
just yet and we don't want average and
只是，我们不希望平均和
average readings yet so so we've got
平均读数，所以我们有
readings and ratings in in we need to
中的读数和等级，我们需要
have a ratings out we know that's
有一个评分，我们知道
correct okay let's try that again
正确，好的，让我们再试一次
nothing is bound to those things yet
那些东西还没有约束
hence it's not gonna work
因此这是行不通的
okay something happened there was a red
好吧发生了什么事
thing just flushed yes okay Cyril eyes
事情只是脸红了是好的，西里尔的眼睛
oh we need the material as the data so
哦，我们需要材料作为数据，所以
again we're gonna be processing data in
再次，我们将在处理数据
this pipeline but in the intermediate
这个管道，但在中间
steps in the pipeline that's gonna write
编写流程的步骤
data to the database and so you have to
数据存储到数据库中，因此您必须
materialize the data and this is the
实现数据，这就是
part that you know it's kind of easy to
您知道这很容易
do it afterwards so you have a materials
之后再做，这样你就有了材料
with long you have serie days long right
只要你有足够的意甲天
like that and then sur des dot double
这样，然后在点点上加倍
nowadays is a sterilizer deserialize ER
如今是对ER进行反序列化的灭菌器
pair okay so again it's a Java framework
配对好了，再次是Java框架
that dealing with object but the Kafka
处理对象，但卡夫卡
is dealing with binary so every time
正在处理二进制文件，所以每次
when we need to save something it's
当我们需要保存一些东西时
graphic or say something outside we need
图形或说一些我们需要的东西
to bring all this kind of fun fun acute
带来所有这种有趣的乐趣
stuff like serialize and deserialize
诸如序列化和反序列化之类的东西
errs and there is a there is like a
错误，有一个像一个
helper classes that allows you to
帮助器类，使您可以
retrieve sterilizer for particular type
检索特定类型的消毒器
like all these like standard types of
像所有这些像标准类型
support it ever supported also like
支持曾经支持过的还喜欢
out-of-the-box there's specific ever
开箱即用的
sterilizer that able to invoke on this
能够对此进行调用的灭菌器
method to dislodge this this stuff so
清除这些东西的方法
I'm gonna run this so first of all
我要先运行
remember I remember what's what's the
记得我记得是什么
topic we're using to store the data yes
我们用来存储数据的主题是
so we can listen to this topic and see
这样我们就可以听听这个话题
if we have anything in this topic so
如果我们在这个话题上有什么话
hammered readings is called AVG ratings
锤击读数称为AVG等级
yep and just erase everything because
是的，只是擦除一切，因为
the value format is in this case it's
在这种情况下，值格式为
not ever it's a just a java format so we
从来没有，这只是一种Java格式，所以我们
would see very beautiful things and
会看到非常美丽的东西，
actually this you notice that it's like
实际上，您注意到它就像
how the Java serialization looked like
Java序列化的样子
like the standard Java serializable it's
就像标准的Java可序列化的
right so this way we're using cool stuff
对，这样我们就可以使用很棒的东西
like a protobuf we're using the Avro
就像protobuf，我们正在使用Avro
we're using thrift we don't using
我们正在使用节俭我们不使用
because it looks ugly right so okay so
因为看起来很丑对，所以还可以
we got so that's clearly doing something
我们知道那显然是在做点什么
right it's running data to that thing oh
正确，它正在向该数据运行数据哦
uh can we turn it into something more
呃我们可以把它变成更多的东西吗
useful
有用
ah no in this case it's not useful
啊，在这种情况下，它没有用
because we don't interesting in this
因为我们对此没有兴趣
result in this case our this like a
结果在这种情况下我们像
generic command line tool need to
通用命令行工具需要
understand Java civilization we need to
了解我们需要的Java文明
bring the classes and all these nonsense
带上课和所有这些废话
okay so now we need a reading as
好吧，现在我们需要阅读
possible yes for for movies so we have
电影可能是这样，所以我们有
these ratings averages and the way how
这些收视率平均值以及如何
we will be doing this we will be joined
我们将这样做，我们将加入
two streams right so this Y you have a
两个流，所以这个Y你有一个
two persons on the street and on the on
两个人在街上和在
the stage how many person you need to to
这个阶段你需要多少人
join two streams so we're gonna say
加入两个流，所以我们要说
first things first public void process
第一件事首先是公共无效过程
incoming movies I'm gonna have to gonna
我要去的即将上映的电影
input two different things here I'm
我在这里输入两个不同的东西
gonna have bindings dots movies yes and
将有绑定点电影是和
that's gonna be a case stream of long
这将是一个漫长的案例
and movie yeah movies okay and then
和电影是电影，然后
input and we don't want the movie itself
输入，我们不想要电影本身
this time we want the the overflow
这次我们要溢出
beings yes yeah so it's gonna be binding
是的，是的，所以它将具有约束力
this dot
这个点
average table or I'm treating yeah yeah
普通桌子还是我在请客
and we want that to be a case stream as
我们希望它成为案例流
well that'll be a long of type so in
好吧，这将是一个很长的类型，所以
order to us not to go to Kafka every
为了我们不要每次都去卡夫卡
time for read this rating because we
是时候读这个评分了，因为我们
have a two separate process kinda sorta
有两个单独的过程
this processor also that the moment
这个处理器也那一刻
where the George did materialize it
乔治在哪里实现
actually created local local states so
实际上建立了当地的地方州
we can retrieve this from the local
我们可以从本地获取
state so that's why we injecting actual
状态，这就是为什么我们注入实际
table
表
it's gonna be no no movies joint yeah
这将是没有电影联合耶
we're joining movies yeah movies the
我们正在加入电影，是的，
joint ratings and yeah yep okay and the
联合评级，是的，是的，
input is gonna be a movie and the double
输入将是电影和双
and the output is going to be a rated
并且输出将是额定的
movie yeah which we don't have we create
是的，我们没有的电影是我们创造的
it by creating a new rated movie which I
通过创建一部新的额定电影，
copied and pasted earlier that's yeah I
是的，复制并粘贴的比较早，是的，我
there you go that's that's yeah that's
你去那就是那是那
coming right here okay
来这里好吗
so I'll create a new rated movie it's
所以我要制作一部新的电影
gonna be a movie dot get movie ID it's
要成为一个电影点，获得电影ID
gonna be movie that get release year
将成为获得发行年份的电影
it'll be a movie that get the title and
这将是一部获得标题的电影，
then finally the double which is the
然后最后是双
it's the the rating it's the average of
这是评分，是平均值
the ratings yep from before
以前的评分是
okay so what's happening what's wrong
好吧，所以发生了什么事
with that seemed okay movies that Joyner
那些看起来不错的电影，乔纳
is it yep where's what's wrong
是的，哪里出了问题
what's it what's the error no it should
这是什么错误是什么不应该
be double yeah okay let's bring our
是双重的，好吧，让我们带上我们
working code sure always good to have
工作代码肯定总是很好
that just in case Kate table key table
以防万一凯特表钥匙表
yeah this one I yeah we need to have a
是的，我需要一个
teeny teeny yeah yeah yeah yeah but you
蝇头蝇头是的是的是的但是你
have a finger table oh it's key table
有一个手指桌哦，这是钥匙桌
yeah hmm and this should be average yep
是的，这应该是平均水平
okay alright so so we have a we need to
好吧，所以我们有一个我们需要
have a put it back into Kafka so in this
把它放回卡夫卡，所以在这个
case we need to have a return key stream
情况下，我们需要一个返回键流
sure okay it's okay so when you have a
当然可以，所以当你有一个
joint yeah yeah we'll have a join
联合是的，我们将加入
extract be valuable from yep join return
从yep join return中提取有价值
join dog this stream okay
加入狗这条流好
and then it'll be send to what will be
然后将其发送到将
this into rated movies movies the final
这入额定电影电影最后
product yep a final thing and in order
产品是最后的事情，并为了
to do that we're gonna say join two
要做到这一点，我们要说加入两个
streams that you know it's a key stream
您知道这是关键流的流
to its a case jam yeah no table its
它的情况下果酱是的，没有桌子
returns key table key table a join to
返回要加入的密钥表密钥表
stream I think we do the ratings that
流我认为我们做的评级
join movies no scroll will have movies
加入电影没有滚动将有电影
it's also key table ok table and in this
这也是关键表确定表，在此
case it turns right thing and will do
如果它变成正确的事情，并且会做
how you extract the variable okay okay
你如何提取变量好吧好吧
no wrong one the at the end right Oh see
没错，最后的权利哦
what I did this so we still have a one
我做了这个，所以我们还有一个
minute so it works
分钟，因此有效
just run it okay so what's that gonna do
只需运行就可以了，那该怎么办
let's just ready to see and we will can
让我们准备好看看，我们将可以
see result in in happy okay just you not
看到结果会幸福，好吧，你不是
a different different one at the rated
额定值不同
yeah
是的
is the loader running yeah
装载机在运行吗
loader running Kafka application it's
加载程序运行的Kafka应用程序
this one yeah I didn't we start analyzer
是的，我不是我们开始分析器
yep so that's the Kafka application we
是的，那是我们的Kafka应用程序
start the analyzer which doesn't know
启动不知道的分析仪
about this new stuff yet yep the waited
关于这个新东西，但是等待
movies a component required of being
电影是必不可少的组成部分
named rated movies oh we have to enable
命名分级电影哦，我们必须启用
that binding so here's our I think you
那个约束，所以这是我们的我想你
yes yes need that I'm gonna need this
是的，需要我会需要这个
alrighty
好吧
ready steady Yom Kippur all right so to
准备稳定的赎罪日好吧，所以
break this the awkward silence I need to
打破这种尴尬的沉默，我需要
probably save maybe some some jokes and
也许可以节省一些笑话，
stuff
东西
what are we missing here sir Oh see how
先生，我们在这里错过了什么
cool here we go
很酷，我们去
thank you very much Josh long place and
非常感谢乔希（Josh）的好地方，
gentleman so what do we do we started
先生，所以我们开始做什么
with basic Kafka started with a Kafka
从基本的卡夫卡开始
template sent messages into the broker
模板将消息发送到代理
that's all very well and good if you've
如果您有的话，那一切都很好
ever used a template before that should
之前曾经使用过模板
be fairly obvious we then moved straight
很明显，然后我们径直向前
into the deep end of the pool and
进入游泳池的深处
started using spring code stream to
开始使用spring代码流
abstract away some of the configuration
抽象一些配置
and the routing and the muse spring cut
布线和缪斯Spring 切
stream with Kafka streams to do a
与卡夫卡流一起做
distributed stream processing it's great
分布式流处理很棒
scale so here's just a small finite data
缩放，所以这只是一个有限的数据
set but of course this the whole point
设置了，但是当然这是全部
of this is that you can now build
这是你现在可以建立
pipelines that handle you know Netflix
处理您的管道知道Netflix
scale kind of stuff right so that's a
正确地缩放东西，这是一个
real opportunity all right thanks
真正的机会好吧谢谢
everybody enjoy yes sure and as always
每个人都喜欢，肯定，一如既往
we are available for advanced
我们可以提供高级
interrogation
审讯
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]